Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=The Ascent of Ling Yun=
=صعود لينغ يون=
=Episode 9=
=الحلقة 9=
(I Will Become His Majesty's Woman)
(سأصبح امرأة جلالته)
Someone!
شخص ما!
Chief Wu is harassing me!
الرئيس وو يضايقني!
Everyone else avoids me.
الجميع يتجنبني.
Yet you boldly approach me.
ومع ذلك فإنك تقترب مني بجرأة.
Because I know you're a good man, my lord.
لأني أعلم أنك رجل طيب يا سيدي.
From the first time you helped me,
منذ المرة الأولى التي ساعدتني فيها،
I knew you are a good man.
لقد عرفت أنك رجل طيب.
All you ever show
كل ما تظهره
is just to make others fear you
هو فقط لجعل الآخرين يخافون منك
and keep a distance.
والحفاظ على مسافة.
Because you fear others getting close.
لأنك تخاف من اقتراب الآخرين منك.
You fear those you care about leaving you eventually.
أنت تخشى أن يتركك الأشخاص الذين تحبهم في النهاية.
(Let's escape together!)
(دعونا نهرب معًا!)
(I'll protect you.)
(سوف أحميك.)
(Run. Live well.)
(أركض. عش جيدًا.)
My lord,
سيدي،
am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
Nonsense.
هراء.
Thank you, my lord.
شكرا لك يا سيدي.
Remember our agreement.
تذكر اتفاقنا.
Ru Yi, are you still mad?
رو يي، هل مازلت غاضبة؟
Everything I told those people was a lie.
كل ما قلته لهؤلاء الناس كان كذبة.
Don't be petty.
لا تكن تافهاً.
Petty?
تافه؟
I heard what you just told them.
لقد سمعت ما قلته لهم للتو.
You agreed to poison Ling Yun, right?
لقد وافقت على تسميم لينغ يون، أليس كذلك؟
Didn't you say you would never bully Ling Yun again?
ألم تقل أنك لن تتنمر على لينغ يون مرة أخرى؟
I'll go tell her now.
سأذهب وأخبرها الآن.
Ru Yi, wait.
رو يي، انتظر.
I'd never dare harm Ling Yun.
لن أجرؤ أبدًا على إيذاء لينغ يون.
My words to Chengxi Palace people
كلماتي لشعب قصر تشنغشي
were all an act.
كان كل ذلك مجرد تمثيل.
I pretended to agree,
تظاهرت بالموافقة،
so Consort Wan's faction
لذا فإن فصيل القرين وان
would go easier on me.
سيكون الأمر أسهل بالنسبة لي.
I'd never hurt Ling Yun.
لن أؤذي لينغ يون أبدًا.
Trust me.
ثق بي.
I-I swear to heaven.
أقسم بالسماء.
I will never harm Ling Yun.
لن أؤذي لينغ يون أبدًا.
If I break this oath,
إذا خالفت هذا القسم،
may lightning strike me dead.
قد يضربني البرق ميتا.
May I rot in the imperial harem
أتمنى أن أتعفن في الحريم الإمبراطوري
as a Servitude Bureau slave forever.
كعبد لمكتب العبودية إلى الأبد.
Your oath makes no sense.
قسمك ليس له معنى.
If lightning kills you,
إذا قتلك البرق،
how would you serve as a slave forever?
كيف ستبقى عبداً إلى الأبد؟
So you believe me?
فهل تصدقني؟
Today's chamber pots aren't scrubbed yet.
لم يتم تنظيف أواني الغرفة اليوم بعد.
Could you help me scrub them?
هل يمكنك مساعدتي في تنظيفهم؟
Cui Wei,
كوي وي,
I've done enough chores for you lately.
لقد قمت بما يكفي من الأعمال المنزلية لك في الآونة الأخيرة.
Come on.
تعال.
Ru Yi, please.
رو يي، من فضلك.
I'm injured right now.
لقد أصبت الآن.
Help me this once.
ساعدني هذه المرة.
When my butt heals,
عندما يشفى مؤخرتي،
I'll scrub yours. Okay?
سأنظف لك. حسنًا؟
Just help me.
فقط ساعدني.
If I don't finish today,
إذا لم أنتهي اليوم،
the matrons will scold me.
سوف توبخني السيدات.
Please help me.
من فضلك ساعدني.
Keep your promise, okay?
حافظ على وعدك، حسنًا؟
I-I swear.
انا اقسم.
Do your own chores from now on.
قم بأعمالك المنزلية بنفسك من الآن فصاعدا.
This is the last time I help.
هذه هي المرة الأخيرة التي أساعد فيها.
- How did this happen?
- كيف حدث هذا؟
- Yes. - Exactly.
- نعم. - بالضبط.
How did this happen?
كيف حدث هذا؟
- When did this happen? - She was fine yesterday.
- متى حدث هذا؟ - كانت بخير بالأمس.
How could this be?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا؟
- This is horrible. - Yes.
- هذا فظيع. - نعم.
She was fine when I saw her.
لقد كانت بخير عندما رأيتها.
How could she be like this?
كيف يمكن أن تكون هكذا؟
I have no idea.
ليس لدي أي فكرة.
Do you know what happened?
هل تعلم ماذا حدث؟
No.
لا.
Ru Yi.
رو يي.
Ru Yi?
رو يي؟
Ru Yi!
رو يي!
Ru Yi.
رو يي.
So tragic.
مأساوية للغاية.
- Chengxi Palace's men came last night. - Was she framed?
- جاء رجال قصر تشنغشي الليلة الماضية. - هل تم توريطها؟
How tragic.
كم هو مأساوي.
Who did this?
من فعل هذا؟
Ru Yi was gone before bedtime.
لقد رحل رو يي قبل موعد النوم.
We found her dead this morning.
لقد وجدناها ميتة هذا الصباح.
Consort Wan has arrived.
وصلت الزوجة وان.
After entering the Servitude Bureau,
بعد دخول مكتب العبودية،
you even forgot basic etiquette?
هل نسيت حتى الآداب الأساسية؟
Seize her.
إمسكها.
How did Ru Yi offend you?
كيف أساء إليك رو يي؟
Why did you kill her?
لماذا قتلتها؟
How dare you question me?
كيف تجرؤ على سؤالي؟
Shun Xi,
شون شي,
cut her tongue out.
قطع لسانها.
Yes, Your Highness.
نعم سموك.
Abusing a maid
إساءة معاملة الخادمة
and disregarding lives,
وتجاهل الأرواح،
you act wildly in Fourteen Bureaus' territory.
أنت تتصرف بعنف في أراضي المكاتب الأربعة عشر.
Aren't you afraid Chief Wu will punish you?
ألا تخاف من أن يعاقبك الرئيس وو؟
Still talking tough before you die?
هل لا تزال تتحدث بقوة قبل أن تموت؟
Do it.
افعلها.
I'll take responsibility.
سأتحمل المسؤولية.
Consort Jing has arrived.
وصلت الزوجة جينغ.
Consort Wan, what are you doing?
زوجة وان، ماذا تفعلين؟
This shameless maid attempted to harm Concubine Zhao
حاولت هذه الخادمة الوقحة إيذاء المحظية تشاو
and framed me days ago.
وأحاطوني منذ أيام.
She deserves to be taught a lesson.
إنها تستحق أن تتعلم درسًا.
Do it.
افعلها.
Why don't you do it?
لماذا لا تفعل ذلك؟
Who dares?
من يجرؤ؟
I was present at the Spring Banquet that day.
لقد كنت حاضرا في حفل الربيع ذلك اليوم.
If I recall correctly,
إذا كنت أتذكر بشكل صحيح،
His Majesty pardoned this maid's life
جلالته عفو عن حياة هذه الخادمة
and sent her here.
وأرسلها إلى هنا.
Today, you make such a grand display here,
اليوم، قمت بعرض رائع هنا،
baying for blood.
النباح من أجل الدم.
His Majesty wants her to live,
جلالته يريد لها أن تعيش،
yet you demand her death.
ومع ذلك تطلب موتها.
Could it be
هل يمكن أن يكون
that you want to defy His Majesty's decree?
أنك تريد أن تتحدى مرسوم جلالته؟
(Consort Jing,)
(الزوجة جينغ)
you saved my life.
لقد انقذت حياتي.
Should the day come
هل يجب أن يأتي اليوم
when you need my help,
عندما تحتاج مساعدتي،
I will spare no effort
لن أدخر أي جهد
to repay your grace.
لسداد نعمتك.
I just happened to pass by today,
لقد مررت بالصدفة اليوم،
witnessed this affair,
لقد شهدت هذه القضية،
and spoke the truth.
وتكلم بالحق.
Every life,
كل حياة،
inside or outside the imperial harem,
داخل أو خارج الحريم الإمبراطوري،
belongs to His Majesty.
ملك لجلالته.
If gratitude is owed,
إذا كان الامتنان واجبا،
thank His Majesty for sparing your life.
اشكر جلالته على إنقاذ حياتك.
Only His Majesty determines our fates.
جلالته وحده هو الذي يحدد مصائرنا.
I shall never forget your edification.
لن أنسى أبدا تنويرك.
(Only His Majesty has the right)
(لجلالته فقط الحق)
(to decide life and death for all.)
(لتقرير الحياة والموت للجميع.)
(I must find a way to gain His Majesty's favor.)
(يجب أن أجد طريقة لكسب رضى جلالته.)
They claim Ru Yi took her own life,
يزعمون أن رو يي انتحرت.
violating palace rules.
انتهاك قواعد القصر.
So she can only be dumped in a mass grave.
لذلك لا يمكن إلا أن يتم إلقاؤها في مقبرة جماعية.
Life is unpredictable.
الحياة غير متوقعة.
Just like this cruel spring chill in March.
تمامًا مثل هذا البرد القارس في الربيع في شهر مارس.
Ru Yi was so kindhearted,
لقد كان رو يي طيب القلب للغاية،
yet heaven subjected her to such cruelty.
ولكن السماء أخضعتها لمثل هذه القسوة.
Where is divine justice?
أين العدالة الإلهية؟
I'll seek a chance to beg mercy for you.
سأبحث عن فرصة لطلب الرحمة لك.
Leave the palace while you can.
أترك القصر بينما يمكنك ذلك.
No.
لا.
I will stay.
سأبقى.
Didn't you ask me
ألم تسألني؟
who I truly am?
من أنا حقا؟
Today, let me tell you.
اليوم دعني أخبرك.
I am Consort Wan's death warrant.
أنا حكم الإعدام لزوجة وان.
She murdered my parents.
لقد قتلت والدي.
I survived countless horrors
لقد نجوت من عدد لا يحصى من الأهوال
just to seek vengeance against her.
فقط من أجل الانتقام منها.
Now,
الآن،
she has taken my only friend Ru Yi
لقد أخذت صديقي الوحيد رو يي
from me too.
مني أيضا.
From this day forth,
من هذا اليوم فصاعدا،
I will use any means,
سأستخدم أي وسيلة،
even losing my soul,
حتى أنني فقدت روحي،
to see Consort Wan
لرؤية القرين وان
torn limb from limb.
تمزق الطرف من الطرف.
But she's an imperial consort.
لكنها زوجة إمبراطورة.
How can you challenge her?
كيف يمكنك تحديها؟
I will become His Majesty's woman.
سأصبح امرأة جلالته.
(I'll make everyone respect me, fear me,)
(سأجعل الجميع يحترموني ويخافونني)
(and bow before my authority.)
(وانحنوا أمام سلطاني).